[CSR] Hi there! You’ve reached Callytics Support, and this is Emily speaking. What can I do for you today?
[Customer] Hello, Emily. I recently upgraded to your premium subscription, but I haven’t seen
any new features activated on my account.
[CSR] Thanks for letting me know. Could you share your account email or username so I
can check what might be causing the issue?
[Customer] Sure, my email is bunyamin@gmail.com.
[CSR] Perfect. One moment while I look that up… It appears there was a slight delay with
the activation. I’ll go ahead and expedite the process. Your premium features should be live within
the next 15 minutes.
[Customer] Great, thank you so much for resolving that!
[CSR] You’re welcome. Is there anything else I can help you with?
[Customer] That’s all. Thanks again!
[CSR] My pleasure. Thanks for reaching out to Callytics, and have a wonderful day!
[Customer] Thank you.